<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-03-30T04:42:27+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Blog about tech, data, finance, etc.</title><subtitle>Blog about tech, data, finance, etc.</subtitle><author><name>LazyTechNerd</name></author><entry><title type="html">About writing</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2022/03/29/about-writing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="About writing" /><published>2022-03-29T11:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-03-29T11:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/2022/03/29/about-writing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/2022/03/29/about-writing.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;about-writing&quot;&gt;About writing&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There once was a quote, I don’t remember where I’ve read it.
It said that &lt;strong&gt;Good Programmer is also a good writer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know if this is accurate. However, as my career grow as a programmer, business &amp;amp; data analyst, or project manager, I’ve realized that I’m not good at writing, whether that is simple report or long articles. I guess that is why I’m starting this blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m a person with various identities. I’ve been in financial industry for more that ten years, however I don’t know how to define myself. Well, I guess this blog will be my practice for better writings and my thoughts on my careers. Also I’m currently studying various things I don’t know how I’ll be posting those but I’ll try to keep record of my studies in order for me to remember better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, I guess you have to begone!! lol 
Because this blog was not meant to be read by various auditions. 
However, if you are like me or interested in my journey to find myself in these busy world of career, I hope my blog can influence you in good way or entertain you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading this nonsence first article.
I hope you have a nice day.
See ya~&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>LazyTechNerd</name></author><summary type="html">About writing</summary></entry></feed>